let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
            "yes",
            "no :("
        ]
    },
    {
    
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is caused by a sudden slip on a fault?",
        answer: "B) earthquake",
        options: [
            "A) volcanic eruption",
            "B) earthquake",
            "C) meteor activity",
            "D) tsunami" 
        ]
    },
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "What do you call the fracture between two blocks of rock?",
    answer: "D) fault",
    options: [
        "A) continental plate",
        "B) stress",
        "C) earthquake",
        "D) fault" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "What kind of fault occurs when the hanging wall moves up over the footwall?",
    answer: "A) reverse fault",
    options: [
        "A) reverse fault",
        "B) thrust fault",
        "C) strike-slip fault",
        "D) normal fault" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "What fault occurs when the hanging wall moves down relative to the footwall?",
    answer: "C) normal fault",
    options: [
        "A) reverse fault",
        "B) thrust fault",
        "C) normal fault",
        "D) strike-slip fault" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "A fault on which the two blocks slide past one another?",
    answer: "D) strike-slip fault",
    options: [
        "A) reverse fault",
        "B) thrust fault",
        "C) normal fault",
        "D) strike-slip fault" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the thinnest layer of the Earth?",
    answer: "A) crust",
    options: [
        "A) crust",
        "B) core",
        "C) mantle",
        "D) inner and outer core" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "What type of stress affects the Earthâ€™s crust wherein it causes the rocks to push against each other?",
    answer: "D) compression stress",
    options: [
        "A) shear stress",
        "B) tension stres",
        "C) confining stress",
        "D) compression stress" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "When stress is applied to all sides of the crust, what type of stress occurs?",
    answer: "C) confining stress",
    options: [
        "A) compression stress",
        "B) shear stress",
        "C) confining stress",
        "D) tension stress" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "What stress forces the rock to pull apart or move away from one another?",
    answer: "B) tension stress",
    options: [
        "A) confining stress",
        "B) tension stress",
        "C) shear stress",
        "D) compression stress" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "What type of stress pushes some of the crust in different directions, rubbing against each other?",
    answer: "A) shear stress",
    options: [
        "A) shear stress",
        "B) compression stress",
        "C) confining stress",
        "D) tension stress", 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "What Philippine government agency is responsible for monitoring the volcanic activities and movement of the Earth crust?",
    answer: "C) PHIVOLCS",
    options: [
        "A) DENR",
        "B) DOH",
        "C) PHIVOLCS",
        "D) Volcano and Earthquake Agency" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "What do you think will occur when the focus of the earthquake happens below or near the ocean?",
    answer: "D) tsunami",
    options: [
        "A) earthquake",
        "B) typhoon",
        "C) landslide",
        "D) tsunami" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "What occurs when the plates are pulled or pushed together?",
    answer: "B) stress",
    options: [
        "A) fault",
        "B) stress",
        "C) earthquake",
        "D) eruption" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "Standing on the fault and looking along its length, what type of strike-slip fault is where the left block moves toward you and the right block moves the opposite way?",
    answer: "C) a left lateral strike-slip fault",
    options: [
        "A) a right lateral strike-slip fault",
        "B) normal fault",
        "C) a left lateral strike-slip fault",
        "D) strike-slip fault" 
    ]
},
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "Standing on the fault and looking along its length, what type of strike-slip fault is where the left block moves toward you and the right block moves the opposite way?",
    answer: "A) a right lateral strike-slip fault",
    options: [
        "A) a right lateral strike-slip fault",
        "B) normal fault",
        "C) a left lateral strike-slip fault",
        "D) strike-slip fault" 
    ]
}
];
